Everyone, please listen to me.
We, as Huma and Gajuma, were walking a path
of coexistence as neighbors and good friends.
Despite that, now we have begun fighting
over the differences between our races...
...and for that reason alone.
Things aren't that simple!
We're just trying to set things right!
Isn't the Queen supposed to be on our side?
What even is race?
Though we differ in appearance,
in times of joy we laugh. and in
times of sorrow we shed tears.
Why is that?
It is because our hearts are the same.
Is that really the Queen?
This is what I believeー
that the body is nothing more than
a vessel which houses the heart.
Even should there be a thing such as raceー
ーIt is not "Gajuma" or "Huma," but rather
one Mankind that shares this earth.
I ask you all to remember...
We have all had times where we've shared
laughter, tears, sorrow, and joy...
...Times where we have been treated with
kindness.
and times where we have eaten delicious
food with one another...
I know of a village, where whenever one of the
ladies bakes pies, everyone gathers together.
It doesn't matter if they're Huma or Gajuma.
Everyone eats together and says "How Delicious!"
Don't let her fool you! She's trying to
win us over because she values her life!
I say this not because I fear death,
but because I believe that living when
everyone you love hates one another
is a fate as cruel as death...
Your Majesty...
That's...not Agarte...
I want you to listen to my last request.
If there is ever a time where you eat a
pie...a peach pie...
I want you to close your eyes and think
about this.
In that heart of yours which
finds it so delicious...
Is there such a thing as race?
Let's move!
Claire!!
Why you...!
!!
Move! Out of my way!
Claire!!
Claire... You're Claire...
I always believed, that no
matter what I looked like
you would come to realize that it was me...
Claire...