The sky is beautiful...
Everything's over, isn't it?
Yeah...
I guess everything turned
out okay in the end?
I am of the same mind.
No, not just me, but everyone
else as well.
Thank you.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!!
I always knew...what would happen
to this world because of me...
And yet... No matter what, I desired
the body of a Huma...
Why... Why was that?
But...I've finally come to realize
what is really important...
At least...as the ruler of this kingdom...
I was able to do this one thing...
for the sake of Mankind.
Please, hang in there!
I'm sorry...for having caused
trouble until the end...
I leave this nation...in your hands...
How could I rule without you?!
So long as you're there, it will be fine....
No...
Please live...
For my sake...
Agarte...
Milhaust...
I've always...loved you...
Agarte...
The conflicts between the races are still ongoing.
This hatred and sorrow isn't going to
disappear any time soon.
But, we need to be able to overcome that...
So that this nation...can experience a rebirth.
Mankind will have to build relationships anew.
It will likely take time, but it can be done.
Yes, I agree.
A time will come where everyone will
see eye to eye. Just like we have.
We are all one Mankind.
When everyone's hearts came together
as one during that disaster,
I'm sure everyone all over the world realized that.
A nation reborn...
I wonder what it'll be like.
At the very least, I'd like to imagine it's
a world where I don't have to wear this anymore.
Are you willing to lend me a hand?
We might have different ways of getting there,
but we all have the same goal, right?
Mankind will follow whatever path you choose.
I feel like we can help guide
them along the way.
I know we can do it.